TASSIANA LAMATINA | Software Engineer

I am a Software Engineer with experience in management and multi-language public speaking. I am passionate about clean, efficient code and the quality of work I provide. I utilize my background in customer service as a foundation in everything I do, always keeping the end-user in mind. My tools are **Javascript**, **HTML**, **CSS**, **Node.js**, **Sequelize**, **React**, **PostgreSQL**, **MongoDB** and **RESTful JSON** routing.

Skills

Languages - JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Python, Typescript | Libraries and Frameworks - React, Node.js, Express.js

Database - PostgreSQL, Sequelize, MongoDB | Other - RESTful Routing JSON jsonWebtoken

Software Development Projects

Mollify - An easy way to keep track of your to-dos.

JULY 2021

- A full stack MERN application built with RESTful routes and API, React, Javascript, MongoDB, bootstrap, JsonWebtoken and Styled Components.
- An application built with the everyday consumer in mind. User specific task list to help simplify their daily chores.

<u>Clambr</u> - A simplified job-search logging application.

JULY 2021

- A project born out of a team collaboration to help anyone who is job-searching to log the jobs they're interested in applying for.
- Full stack application made with RESTful API, React, Javascript, bootstrap, MongoDB, Express RESTful routes, axios, jsonWebtoken, DOM manipulation, Styled Components, Asana, Figma, Zeplin, bcrypt, Rowdy-Logger and Mongoose.

Best Buy Deals - Full-stack application that allows users to search special deals within Best Buy API.

JUNE 2021

- Made RESTful API fetch calls to an **Express**, **Node.js** backend handling all create, read, update, delete (**CRUD**) operations, and tested all backend routes during development using **Postman**.
- Created layout using HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap and Tailwind in a 5-day sprint.

Professional Experience

General Assembly - Software Engineer Fellow | Remote

MAY 2021 - July 2021

• A learning environment focused on remote group development, as well as comprehensive full-stack software engineering in an intensive, 12week, 450+ hour program.

Freelance- Web Developer | Remote

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

- Created Dynamic Websites with Wordpress that were user-friendly, effective, and appealing as well as improving coding of CSS and PHP to enhance functionality and user experience.
- Redesigned existing websites to improve user experience and incorporated SEO techniques thereby increasing daily traffic by as high as 36%.
- Worked closely with the owner and marketing team to develop a strategy and plan website flow.
- Maintained a strong communication line with stakeholders to implement vision and deliver materials on time.

T-Mobile - General Retail Manager | Los Angeles, CA

SEPTEMBER 2018 - JUNE 2019

- Enhanced operational success in three locations that grossed an average of \$4.8 million yearly through effective staffing, strong training, adherence to safety regulations and well-timed customer service.
- Effectively increased conversion of traffic by 28% in three months with coaching and training.
- Reviewed daily performance data to monitor and measure productivity, goal progress and activity levels.

• Managed multi million dollar yearly-budget implementations, employee reviews, training, schedules and contract negotiations.

Armor Electric - Executive Assistant To CEO | Los Angeles, CA

NOVEMBER 2014 - OCTOBER 2018

- Coordinated detailed oriented domestic and international travel arrangements, including booking airfare, hotel and ground transportation for all crew members.
- Contributed to smooth business operations by planning and organizing meetings, conferences, including conference calls and customer appointments up to 15 times daily.
- Worked with senior management to initiate new projects as well as assist in various operational processes that would communicate better with the updated website.
- Completed all required and suggested training to match employees including CALOSHA and basic Electrical Training Courses.

EDUCATION

General Assembly | Remote **Software Engineering Immersive**

2021

Full-stack software engineering immersive student in an intensive, twelve-week, 450+ hour program focused on product development fundamentals, object-oriented programming, MVC frameworks, data modeling, and team collaboration strategies. Developed a portfolio of individual and group projects.